[Music]
[Laughter]
right guys have been sent a find pouch
from a company on amazon which i'll put
the links down in the uh
description below
they sent me this uh finest pouch to do
a review on
uh so we're gonna do today is quickly
show you
the finest pouch and what it can take
and hold and then the next video i'll be
out melt detecting
using the fines pouch putting it into
action all right first of all
you've got somewhere where you can put
your name
if you lose it
at the front you've got a nice zip
pocket
just in there
you've got a velcro pocket just in the
other which is quite
big put your whole hand in there
on the side there
you've got your drinks bottle
holder
on the bottom
you've got some padded feet so don't
wear wear out for the ground this is
quite a thick material
it is waterproof even though it hasn't
got cover doesn't matter
on the other side there you've got a
place where you pinpoint you
um it's a little bit tight for some
pinpointers
so you might be able to um stretch those
a bit
obviously you can put your um calabina
there carabiner that's it hook it on
and
your belt straps
it doesn't come with a belt so you have
to use your own belt
so what we'll do is i'm going to put it
on and then show you what it's like
right
so there you go
you've got your drinks bowl
on the side
inside the main pocket
you can put your digging trowel
fits in there quite nice
and the other pocket there
deep down
spray water
there you go just drops in
there the front pouch
is where you store all your goodies for
your fine spouts
friends box
and there's your pinpointer
easy to handle straight in
off you go
so yeah so it's
quite a fair size
um
i like it
i'm gonna be using this all the time
from now right
don't forget guys
links in the description
uh leave a comment
and um we'll see you out on the field
detecting some reset the best that you
can get they haven't found it yet but
they soon will